In this video,
how much salary does a sales manager get in ICC Prudential Life Insurance Company? This
salary data is
based on 164 salaries, that is, 164
people have told their salary,
according to that this data has been provided to you, so the
average total pay of the one, that is, the
gross salary that has been calculated is ₹700000,
you get an approximate salary of ₹700000 gross and
apart from this, the additional pay that you get separately,
which you can call bonus and sensitive,
is
₹126000 for year, so the approximate close that you get for a
sales manager,
you will see below, it is an average base pay,
you get an approximate salary of 630000,
and you can get a separate bonus, the
approximate close of the yearly is ₹1 lakh, if
you liked the salary structure of sales manager
in ICC Prudential Life
Insurance Company video,
then like and subscribe